{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Sliding Door Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40220/":{"taskOID":40220,"originalTaskOID":40220,"setID":527,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500741,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this door project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this door project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":5244,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace an old one of the same type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one of the same type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5245,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace an old one with different type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one with different type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200961,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install where one did not previously exist","answerDisplayText":"Install where one did not previously exist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200962,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing door","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500742,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of door would you like installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200963,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Exterior sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5028,"questionDisplayText":"Sliding Door Supplier","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will supply the sliding door?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1614,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Contractor","answerDisplayText":"Contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500641,"questionDisplayText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","shortQuestionText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500741,"questionDisplayText":"Project Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes this door project?","shortQuestionText":"What best describes this door project?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":5244,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace an old one of the same type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one of the same type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5245,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace an old one with different type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one with different type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200961,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install where one did not previously exist","answerDisplayText":"Install where one did not previously exist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200962,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing door","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5244,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Replace an old one of the same type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one of the same type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5245,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Replace an old one with different type","answerDisplayText":"Replace an old one with different type","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200961,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Install where one did not previously exist","answerDisplayText":"Install where one did not previously exist","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200962,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Repair existing door","answerDisplayText":"Repair existing door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500742,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Door","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of door would you like installed?","shortQuestionText":"What type of door would you like installed?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200963,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Exterior sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3315,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Interior","answerDisplayText":"Interior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2315,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Exterior","answerDisplayText":"Exterior","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200963,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Exterior sliding door","answerDisplayText":"Exterior sliding door","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5028,"questionDisplayText":"Sliding Door Supplier","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who will supply the sliding door?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1614,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Contractor","answerDisplayText":"Contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3063,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Homeowner","answerDisplayText":"Homeowner","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1614,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Contractor","answerDisplayText":"Contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":500641,"questionDisplayText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","shortQuestionText":"How many doors do you want installed or replaced?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10011,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"1","answerDisplayText":"1","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10012,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"2","answerDisplayText":"2","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10013,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"3","answerDisplayText":"3","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":473,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"4 or more","answerDisplayText":"4 or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/40220/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40220,"taskName":"Sliding Door - Install","taskDescription":"Install or Replace Sliding Doors","xmTaskDescriptor":"Sliding Door Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":4712,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Sliding mirror track barn entry","textMessagingName":"Sliding Door","rolloverLongDesc":"For swinging doors, see Install Door.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes installations or replacements.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Sliding Doors.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Sliding Door Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Sliding Glass or Screen Door","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":22,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Sliding Door Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Sliding Door - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Sliding Door Project","urlName":"Sliding-Door-Install","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Sliding Door Installers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor Sliding Glass, Screen Door Install \u0026 Cost","searchKeywords":"Sliding,mirror,track,barn,entry,,screen,installsliding,wood,shower,patio,french,interior,front,glass,exterior,security,installations,closet,Doors,bedroom,automatic,Door","emcCategoryOid":-12024,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":527,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}